本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
嘿嘿  小查莉  快看这个
Hey, Charlie, check this out.
这幅景象以前可从未被披露过
Here's something nobody has ever seen before.
盖比自己在梳他的头发呀
<i>Gabe is brushing his hair</i>
你非得把我们干的所有鸡毛蒜皮的事儿都录下来吗
Do you have to videotape everything we do?
这又不是真人秀节目
This isn't a reality show.
哈  我知道这已经脱离现实了
Oh, I know it's not reality because
因为那小子不用别人啰嗦就自己去洗了个澡
he took a shower without being asked.
你知道我在想什么吗
You know what I think?
我觉得啊  你对谁动心了吧
I think you like someone.
是又怎么样  又不是什么大事
What if I do? No big deal.
没开玩笑吧  你的初恋可绝对是大事一件呐
Are you kidding? Your first crush is a huge deal.
听着  男女异性相吸
Look, she is a girl. I'm a guy.
这种事每天都会发生
These things happen every day.
可没发生在你身上过呀
Not to you.
我知道呀  姐姐你也不相信吧
I know. Can you believe it?
好了  孩子们  快点  我们走吧
Hey, kids, come on, let's go.
PJ  亲爱的  你放学后能照看一下查莉吗
P.J. Honey, can you watch charlie after school?
我得上班
I have to work.
不行啊  我也有工作
I can't. I'm working too.
如果你觉得行  那我可以带着查莉一起送外卖去
I can take charlie with me if you want.
你想帮忙你大哥去送鸡肉外卖吗
You want to help your big brother deliver chicken?
不然你也可以选去医院
Or you could come to the hospital
帮妈妈给病人换尿盆
And help mommy change bedpans.
还是你带着她吧
You take her.
盖比  你是不是用了刮胡水
Gabe, are you wearing aftershave?
一点点啊
A little.
你干嘛要用那个  你又没有胡子可刮
Why would you do that? You're not shaving yet.
如果凡事都要问个为什么的话
As long as we're being logical,
那你为什么仍然保留着梳子呢
why do you still have a comb?
赶快上车
Get in the car.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late, and dad jokes
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
■
翻译： 山鹰逢羽
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
There it is up on the roof
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
■
校订  后期： WaitinZ
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记  第一季第十二集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E12  Kit and Kaboodle
很好  现在是我的好机会
<i>Okay, this is my chance.</i>
可别搞砸了
<i>Don't blow it.</i>
快去跟她搭讪吧
<i>Say something to her.</i>
嗨  凯蒂
<i>H-h-hi, Kit.</i>
你好啊  凯蒂
<i>Hellllooo, Kit!</i>
哟  哟  哟  凯蒂
<i>Yo yo yo, Kit!</i>
我嘴巴好干啊
<i>My mouth's so dry.</i>
得先喝点果汁
<i>I need juice.</i>
这是果汁啦  不是尿裤子
It's juice. This is not pee.
进展不错
<i>That went well.</i>
你姐姐在家吗
Is your sister home?
在
Yes.
谁啊
Who was that?
达布尼太太来问个蠢问题
Mrs. Dabney with her stupid questions.
我的问题还有后续呢
I have a follow-up question--
我可以找你姐姐问话吗
May I speak to your sister?
有什么我可以效劳的  达布尼太太
What can I do for you, mrs. Dabney?
我要出城几天
I'm going out of town for a couple of days
我想知道你是不是够友善
And I was wondering if y'd be kind enough
可以帮我照顾我的猫卡不多
to look after my cat Caboodle.
哦  我不晓得耶  我最近忙死了
Oh, I don't know. I'm awfully busy.
一天付你二十块
I'll pay you $20 a day.
我的时间表刚刚空出来
My schedule just opened up.
很好
Mm-hmm.
我可以信任你的  对吧
I can trust you, right?
当然了
Of course.
你确实算是
You do seem to be
邓肯家孩子们中最不烦人的一个
the least disturbed of all the Duncan kids.
几乎算是很好的恭维话了呢
What an almost sweet thing to say.
你要知道  卡不多
You need to know that Caboodle
是我在这世上最珍贵的宝贝
Is the most important thing in the world to me.
达布尼先生最近怎样啊
How's mr. Dabney doing?
反正照我说的做  好好待卡不多
Like I said, love that Caboodle.
谁呀
<i>Who is it?</i>
咕唧鸡外卖
Kwikki Chikki.
哦  你好
Oh, hello.
总价是二十一元七分
Hi, it's $21.07.
好的  那这个小可爱是谁啊
Oh, okay. Who is this cutie pie?
我叫PJ
I'm p.J.
我说的是另一个小可爱
I meant the other cutie pie.
喔  她叫查莉  是我的小妹妹
Oh, this is Charlie. She's my baby sister.
难道她不是这世上最让人珍爱的小宝贝吗
Why, isn't she the most precious thing in the whole world?
是啊  我妈妈在医院里
Yeah, my mom's at the hospital,
所以我要照看她
so I'm looking after her.
哦  你这个小可怜
Oh, you poor dear.
不用找钱了
Keep the change.
你确定吗  这可差不多有二十元的小费耶
Are you sure? This is almost a $20 tip.
唉  你比我更需要它
Oh, you need it more than I do,
拿去给在医院的妈妈买点什么吧
What with your mom being in the hospital and all.
咦  你以为我妈妈是住
Oh, you think my mom is in--
我不骗您  我们确实很艰难
I'm not gonna lie to you. It's been hard.
请享用您的鸡肉吧
Enjoy your chicken.
查莉啊  欢迎加入鸡肉外卖行业
Charlie, welcome to the chicken delivery business.
每天喂两次猫粮
Give him dry food twice a day
并确保它的水碗里总是加满水
And make sure his water bowl is always filled.
还有我妹妹维吉妮亚稍后会过来一起玩
Oh, and my sister Virginia is coming by later for a play date.
你想要我和你妹妹一起玩
You want me to have a play date with your sister?
不是你  是卡不多
Not you-- Caboodle.
维吉妮亚会带来她的猫  斯坦利
Virginia brings her cat Stanley over.
猫的名字这么滑稽啊
What a ridiculous name for a cat.
你说卡不多吗
Caboodle?
我是说斯坦利
Stanley
哦  我要走了
Oh, I should go.
但我的小卡不多多可就要不高兴了
But so my little Caboodie won't make a scene,
你要逗逗他让他分心
You need to distract him.
我要装成耗子吗
Should I pretend to be a mouse?
当然
Yes.
我是说笑的
I was joking.
我可不说笑
I wasn't.
我看这猫现在就挺好啊
The cat seems fine to me.
我可是付钱让你干事的
I'm paying you.
现在放下他然后去扮耗子吧
Now put him down and act like a mouse.
吱吱  吱吱
Squeak squeak.
你能扮得更像一点么
You can do better than that.
要龇牙咧嘴皱鼻子
Bare your teeth, wiggle your nose
扮成你正在偷奶酪吃
And act like you're eating a piece of cheese.
现在继续这样扮二十分钟
Now keep doing that for 20 minutes,
他就会很安分的  再见了  小卡不多宝贝
And he should be fine. Goodbye, my Caboodle.
泰迪宝贝  你在找什么东西吗
Teddy honey, did you lose something?
找我刚丢的尊严
Only my dignity.
妈妈  你能帮我一下吗
Mom, can you help me with something?
当然可以啦  亲爱的  你要我帮什么
Sure, honey. What can I do for you?
那个嘛  我有个朋友
Well, I have this friend
他想要知道怎么和女孩们聊天
And he needs to know how to talk to girls.
这朋友叫什么名字
Does this friend have a name?
诺曼（无名氏）
No-orman.
诺曼
真是个奇怪的名字
That's an odd name.
那个  我想他是挪威来的
Well, I think he's from No-orway.
盖比宝贝啊  我是你妈耶
Gabe honey, I'm your mom.
你不用觉得难为情的
You don't have to be embarrassed
来告诉我你的初恋故事吧
About telling me about your first crushy-wushy.
我还是到网上去搜索一下好了
I'm just gonna go look it up on the internet.
别别别  没问题的
No no no, it's okay.
对不起  对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
那么  你之前跟她说过什么没
Okay, so what have you said to her so far?
嗯  我有说啊
Um, I said,
我说的是“这是果汁  不是尿”
"that was juice, not pee."
然后她就走掉了
And then she walked away.
哦  不会吧  无名氏
Oh, no-orman.
每次我一靠近她
Every time I get near her,
我就手心冒汗  心脏扑通乱跳
My heart starts pounding, my hands get all sweaty
话都说不出来
And I can't speak.
哦  你痴情得够严重的
Oh, you've got it bad.
我想起自己的初恋时光了
I remember my first crush.
你的初恋不是老爸吗
Was it dad?
当然  怎会不是呢
Sure, why not?
那我该怎么办啊  我要怎么对她开口呢
So what do I do? How do I talk to her?
听好啊  当你觉得开始紧张时
Well, when you start to get a little nervous,
你就去问她问题  让她去讲话就行了
Just ask her questions. Let her do the talking.
找到你们共同的兴趣
Find things you have in common.
所以只要问问她然后自己听她回答吗
So just ask her stuff and listen to the answers?
听上去倒蛮简单的
That sounds easy.
你可以的
Sure.
感情上的事不过是小菜一碟
Relationships are a piece of cake.
这就是为何已婚人士总是这么幸福快乐
That's why married people are always so happy.
老爸以前追你时说话会紧张吗
Did dad ever get nervous talking to you?
哦  你爸和我第一次约会时
Oh, when your dad and I first started dating
我们基本上没讲什么话  大多数时间我们都是在
We didn't do a lot of talking. Mostly we just--
在做什么
Just what?
在玩西洋棋
Played checkers--
玩了很久很久的西洋棋呢
Lots and lots of checkers.
嘿  老爸
<i>Hey, dad.</i>
嘿
Hey.
明天下午是你要照看查莉的  对吧
You're taking care of Charlie tomorrow afternoon, right?
我想是轮到我了
I believe I am.
你看  我在想也许可以
You know, I was thinking maybe
带着她一起去送外卖
she should come to work with me.
为什么
Why?
因为我觉得  在泰迪和盖比小的时候
Because I feel I didn't do enough to help out
我都没有怎么帮上足够的忙
When Teddy and Gabe were babies.
你说足够吗  你根本就没帮忙
Enough? You didn't do anything.
我知道
I know.
现在我觉得内疚了
And it haunts me.
你还会为这个内疚啊
It haunts you?
真的呀
Yes.
所以我想通过照顾查莉来补偿你们
That's why I have to make it up to you with Charlie.
行啊
Okay.
我会想你的  老爸
I'll miss you, dad.
哦  那小鬼肯定在打什么小算盘
Oh, that boy's up to something.
看来我得去管管这事儿
I should probably get into this.
算了  反正他就在楼上跑不掉
Eh, he's all the way upstairs.
聆听并寻找共同话题
<i>Listen and find things in common.</i>
听她说  找到共同点
-好啊  -好啊
- Hi.  - Hi.
给我说说你自己吧
Tell me about yourself.
为什么
Why?
我是说如果你愿意的话
I mean, only if you want to.
好吧  你想知道些什么呢
Okay, what do you want to know?
说说你的家人吧
Tell me about your family.
哦  家人啊
Oh, the family.
其实没什么好说的
Actually there's not much to tell.
我是独生女
I'm an only child.
我也是
Me too.
那很好啊
Cool.
还有什么吗
What else?
嗯  我爸妈离婚了
Well, my parents are divorced.
我家也是
Mine too.
你跟谁住啊
Who do you live with?
你又是跟着谁呢
我跟我妈的
My mom.
我也是啊
Me too.
哇  我们真的有很多共同点
Wow, we really have a lot in common.
你知道吗  我早就有这个预感了
You know, I had a feeling we might.
你想要吃一半花生酱三明治吗
Want half of a peanut-butter sandwich?
谢谢不用了  我对花生过敏
No, thanks. I'm allergic to peanuts.
我也是
Me too.
你不太爱动  是吧
You dnt do much, do you?
嘿看着  去抓呀
Hey hey, catch.
还是别动好了
Or stay.
乖猫咪
Good cat.
达布尼太太  你怎么回来啦
Mrs. Dabney, why are you back here?
哦  我不是伊斯泰尔啦  我是她妹妹维吉妮亚
Oh, I'm not Estelle. I'm her sister Virginia.
哇  你看上去真的很像达布尼太太
Wow, you really look like Mrs. Dabney.
但是我有微笑纹
Except for my laugh lines.
伊斯泰尔是一条也没有
Estelle doesn't have any of those.
盖比  这位是达布尼太太的孪生妹妹维吉妮亚女士
Gabe, this is mrs. Dabney's twin sister Virginia.
他是我弟弟盖比
This is my brother gabe.
哦  你看上去是个很棒的小男孩
Oh, you look like a nice little boy.
要不要吃糖果呀
Would you like some candy?
除非你自己先吃一个我看
Only if you eat one first.
你就跟小恶魔一样可爱呢
You're as cute as the dickens.
好吧  真是古怪的感觉
Okay, this is dang freaky.
好了  斯坦利
Okay, Stanley.
去和卡不多玩玩吧
Let's go play with Caboodle.
我们来啰
Here we go.
啊哦
Uh-oh.
怎么啦
What's wrong?
卡不多每次见到斯坦利  一定都会很兴奋的呀
Caboodle always gets excited when Stanley arrives.
他已经这样躺在沙发上一天了
He's just been lying on the couch all day.
你觉得他是病了吗
Do you think he's sick?
你最好祈祷没有
You'd better hope not.
我可不希望是在你照看他的时候
I'd hate to be in your shoes
我姐的宝贝发生什么意外
If something happened to my sister's baby.
可这又不是我的错
Well, it's not my fault.
她应该能理解的  对吧
She'd understand that, right?
哦对啊  她是个特别能宽容理解的人
Oh, yeah. She's very understanding.
来吧  卡不多  打起精神来
Come on, caboodle, perk up.
一点反应也没
This does not look good.
哦  我知道怎样可以让你有精神了
Oh, I know what will cheer you up--
耗子先生  对不对啊
Mr. Mouse, right?
这也没用
This does not look good either.
所以我们全家都同心协力来帮忙照顾小查莉
The whole family's pitching in to help out with Charlie,
因为我妈妈在医院里
Because my mom's in the hospital.
谢谢你
Thank you.
也要谢谢你呀
And thank <i>you.</i>
这本来是她的万圣节装扮
Used to be her Halloween costume,
但是因为妈妈在医院
But with mom in the hospital,
我们没钱给她买冬天的外套了
We can't afford to buy her a winter coat--
一件新的冬装啊
A new winter coat.
你妈妈好些了吗
Is your mom any better?
还是老样子
The same,
但我们都在努力坚强
But we're trying to be brave.
可怜的小东西
You poor thing.
唉
Aww.
对我这小妹来说是最难受的
It's hardest on the little ones.
每次我们去医院看妈妈
Whenever we visit mom in the hospital,
查莉都会这样
Charlie does this.
妈妈  妈妈  妈妈
Mama mama mama.
沃伦  赶紧出来
Warren, get out here!
把你的钱包也拿来
And bring your wallet!
谢谢您这么临时赶过来  塔希医生（音屁股）
Thanks for coming on such short notice, Dr. Tushy.
那个词发音是  图希
It's pronounced "Tushy."
你不用谢我
you don't have to thank me.
卡不多·达布尼是我最喜爱的病人之一
Caboodle Dabney is one of my favorite patients.
我不知道兽医也可以上门看诊的呢
I didn't know veterinarians made house calls.
兽医是不会  我是精神治疗师
Oh, they don't. I'm a therapist.
给猫咪做精神治疗
A therapist for cats?
也接受禽类服务  不过决不能安排在同一时间
And birds. But never at the same time.
你就试试看犯那么一次错好了
You only make that mistake once.
唔  这样啊
Uh-huh. Huh.
原来如此
Oh.
那么卡不多到底怎么啦
So what's wrong with caboodle?
看来他的灵光不稳  他的元神也不协调了
Well, his aura is off. His chakras are out of line.
他大便怎么样
How's his poop?
很好啊  你的呢
Fine. How's yours?
哦  那可有点属于私隐范围了
Well, that's a little personal,
不过既然你问了  我就说吧  我的特棒而且越来越好了
But since you ask, super good and getting better.
也许我们应该还是说回到猫咪吧  特希医生
Maybe we should get back to the cat, Dr. Tushy.
是图希啦
It's "Tushy."
突希
Tushy.
不对  图希
Huh-uh, tushy.
土希吗
Tushy?
图希  图希  图希
Tushy Tushy Tushy.
我可以叫你的名而不是姓吗
Do you have a first name?
我名字是提希
Tish.
提希·图希
Tish Tushy?
要加医生的敬称哦
"Doctor."
随便吧  你能治好他吗
Anyway, can you fix him?
不行
No.
不过你可以  卡不多觉得是被遗弃了
But you can. Caboodle is feeling abandoned.
他需要安全感
He needs to know he's safe and secure.
现在你闭上双眼  把你的思想传递给他
Now close your eyes and send him a thought
让他知道你对他的爱和关心
To let him know you care.
你能不能就给他打一针什么的吗
Can't you give him a shot or--?
把你的思想传递给他吧
Send him a thought.
传递思想  传递思想
Send him a thought. Send him a thought.
你现在有什么想法
Do you have a thought?
喔  我可是有好些想法呢
Oh, I'm having a few of them.
凯蒂
Kit.
你好啊  盖比
Hi, Gabe.
你怎么来啦
What are you doing here?
我跟妈妈讲了你的事
I told my mom all about you
我们就是想过来问候一下
And we just wanted to say hi.
是啊  凯蒂真幸运能遇上
Yeah, it is so wonderful that Kit met someone
和我们相同境遇的家庭  是多么好的事啊
With a family just like ours.
好啊
Okay.
我们可以进去吗
Do you mind if we come in?
当然可以  我猜没问题
Yeah, sure, I guess.
好的
Okay.
不好意思  我去去就回
You know, I'll actually be right back.
随意哈
Okay.
我遇到大麻烦了  你在干嘛呀
I have a big problem. What are you doing?
我在重建卡不多的灵光呢  呸
I'm readjusting caboodle's aura. Duh.
我遇到大麻烦了
I'm in big trouble.
出什么事了
What's wrong?
我喜欢的那个女孩子带着她妈妈来我们家了
The girl I like is here with her mom.
那有什么问题啊
What's wrong with that?
我告诉她说爸妈离婚了
I told her mom and dad are divorced
还有我是独生子  现在我该怎么办
And I'm an only child. What am I gonna do?
好吧  首先你要先冷静下来
Okay, the first thing you're gonna do is calm down.
你的负面能量正使猫咪更消沉呢
Your negative energy is upsetting the cat.
你一定要帮帮我呀
You gotta help me.
好了  放松
Okay, relax,
不然之后你大便就也会有麻烦了
Or later you're gonna have trouble with your poop.
泰迪
Teddy.
好的  我出去打发他们
Fine, I'll go and get rid of them.
等等  不能让她们知道你是我姐姐呀
Wait, they can't know you're my sister.
对  那么我假装成别人
Right, so I will be somebody else.
嗨  我是泰迪  是钟点工  看到没
Hi, I'm Teddy, the housekeeper.  See?
你好  我是黛娜  我女儿凯蒂
Hi, I'm Dana. This is Kit.
你为什么把猫咪戴在身上呀
Why are you wearing a cat?
因为在我的祖国有句谚语叫做
Because in my country we have a saying
猫咪在怀  房子不坏
"the house looks its best when a cat's on your chest."
那是什么国家呀
What country is that?
加拿大
Canada.
邓肯太太不在家  我还要打扫屋子
Mrs. Duncan isn't home and I have a house to clean,
所以在我家乡的俗话就是 “去吧”
So as we say in my country, "oot."
去吧  去吧
"oot oot."
好的  能请你转告他妈妈说我们来过吗
Okay, could you just tell her we stopped by?
没问题
You betcha.
嗨  大家好
Hey, everybody.
那是谁啊
Who's that?
那是送鸡块外卖的伙计
That's the chicken delivery guy.
姐们  你戴着个猫干啥啊
Dude, what's with the cat?
不管你的事
None of your business.
还有别叫我姐们  送鸡块外卖的小子
And don't call me "dude," chicken delivery guy.
现在跟我到玄关外去
Now come out to the porch
我来教你怎么用门铃
Where I will teach you how to use a doorbell.
你知道奇怪之处在哪里吗
You know what's weird?
他根本没带鸡块来啊
He didn't have any chicken.
他只是过来先给我们送点餐单
He's just here to take our order.
然后别的伙计再送餐过来
Then another guy comes and delivers it.
这是个很低效的运作系统
It's not a good system.
对  我就是送鸡肉外卖的伙计
I'm the chicken delivery guy.
看到没
See?
这真是个多么可爱的宝宝  她是不是
That is such an adorable baby. Is she--?
她是现在的促销活动宣传  对吧  PJ
Part of the promotion. Right, P.J.,
PJ是不是你的名字来着
Which may or may not be your name?
说的对  现在是我们的促销期
That's right. A promotion.
咕唧鸡店正在宣传
Kwikki chikki is introducing
烤嫩肉肋排呀
Baby back ribs.
他们居然真的让你带着一个宝宝到处跑
And they make you carry around a baby?
是公司上层决定的
That comes from corporate.
他们根本不知道基层员工的艰辛
They have no idea what it's like out in the field.
看谁来啦  他是谁呀
Look who's here. Who is here?
嗨  我是鲍伯
Hi, I'm Bob.
他是个除害专员
The exterminator.
是啊  但我比那更高阶一点
Yeah, I'm a little more than that.
你干嘛背着个猫在身上
Why are you wearing a cat?
哎呀  别管猫了  后院里有一只臭鼬
Oh, forget the cat. There is a skunk in the backyard
我要求你赶快去把那玩意给除了
And I demand you go exterminate it right now.
你在说什么胡话
What are you talking about?
臭鼬白天根本不出来的
Skunks don't come out during the day.
好吧  那你就出去告诉他们别出来
Well, then go out and tell him that.
很抱歉
Sorry about that.
他很专业的  就是有些啰嗦
He does good work, but he's a little chatty.
老妈  不会吧
Mom? No!
好吧  你也好
Well, hello to you too.
你好啊
Hello.
你好我是黛娜  是凯蒂的妈妈
Hi, I'm Dana. I'm Kit's mom.
我是艾米
I'm Amy.
这个宝宝好可爱呀
This baby is so cute.
她果然是吧
Isn't she?
她确实让我都想吃烤肋排了
She sure makes me want some baby back ribs.
你说啥
Beg pardon?
后院根本没臭鼬  哦你回来啦  甜心
No skunk back there. Oh, hey, sweetie.
亲爱的
Hey.
哇  你对灭害员可真够友好的
Wow, you're very friendly with the exterminator.
我确实每晚都睡在他旁边
I do sleep next to him every night.
我都不知道你已经有男朋友了
I didn't realize you had a boyfriend.
他有啥
She's got a what?
灭害员是你的男朋友呀
The exterminator is your boyfriend.
这个灭害专家是我的老公
The exterminator is my husband.
那你是再婚啰
So you remarried?
我从来没离过婚啊
I was never divorced.
可是凯蒂告诉我你离婚了
Well, Kit told me you were.
因为那是盖比告诉我的
Because that's what gabe told me.
我也许是说了一个特别微不足道的谎话
I may have told a teeny little lie.
对不起  我只是希望你喜欢我
Sorry. I just wanted you to like me.
盖比  你应该对我说实话的
Gabe, you should have just told me the truth.
我知道  我现在保证
I know. And I promise,
从现在起  我将一直完全诚实地对待你
From now on I'll always be completely honest with you.
我回来啦
I'm back.
这人又是谁啊
Now who's this?
她要么是友善到处发糖的维吉妮亚
That's either virginia who's nice and gives out candy
要么就是她那邪恶的孪生姐姐  达布尼太太
Or Mrs. Dabney-- her evil twin.
我们离开这里吧
We're out of here.
好吧  查莉  好消息是卡不多没事了
Well, Charlie, the good news is Caboodle's fine.
总算知道了  他需要的只是去垃圾桶附近转转
Turns out all he needed was a trip to the litter box.
但坏消息是  盖比和凯蒂的罗曼史算是完了
But the bad news is Gabe's romance with Kit is over.
不过  我的好消息是
Well, the good news is
我再也不用洗澡了
I don't have to shower anymore.
这还真是好消息
That's really good news.
那么要是你遇到你的哥哥盖比
So if your brother gabe
想要过来抱抱你
goes to give you a hug,
可就祝你好运喽  查莉
Well, good luck, Charlie.
别担心  我才不会抱你呢
Don't worry. That won't happen.
老妈  查莉明天要和我一起去上班
Hey, mom, Charlie and I have to work a double tomorrow.
怎么搞的  你干嘛一直要带着查莉出去上班呢
What? Why do you keep taking Charlie to work?
因为我爱她啊
Because I love her.
没人去吗
Nobody?
有什么需要吗
May I help you?
我就是想拿这盘菜给你
I just wanted to drop off this casserole.
请问为啥
Excuse me?
那个  因为PJ的妈妈在住院
Well, with P.J.'s mom being in the hospital
他几乎要独自抚养着小查莉
And him practically having to raise Charlie on his own--
真是太感伤了
It's just so sad.
啊  你以为
You think--
天  闻起来真香啊
Gosh, that smells good.
确实很感伤啊
It is sad.
-我觉得当人们在需要时  -多谢你了
- I find when people are in need-- - Thank you.
孩子们  晚饭有了
Kids, dinner's ready.
门开着呢
It's open.
怎么还有一个
There's another one?
又来了一个啊
见鬼啊
What?
我可不知道
I don't know.
我们就是来自威斯康星州举世闻名的五胞胎姐妹
We're the world famous quintuplets, Wisconsin.
我们可是一九五八年最著名的传奇故事呢
We were the biggest news story of 1958.
这次本该是家庭团圆会的
This was supposed to be a family reunion.
怎么没聚成
What happened?
伊斯泰尔把我们赶出来了  那女人真是有病
Estelle kicked us out. That woman's not right.
深有同感啊
Tell me about it!